infomarketingblog.com 2010-06-22

# Privacy Policy

Infomarketingblog.com is committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy details how we use your personal identifying information. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice to you. Please review this document each time you visit us or use any of our tools or services.

It is our policy, except as noted below, not to sale, trade, lease, give away or otherwise release your personal information, which includes your name, physical address (business or home), home or business telephone number and your e-mail address. 

We collect your name and email opt-ins for the purpose of sending unconfirmed opt-in based email to you. We do not conduct any marketing for any third parties and we do not sell, lease, trade or otherwise allow any third party to have access to our email lists. As always, you may opt-out of receiving any email from us if you wish by following the opt-out procedure set forth in the emails that you receive from us.

**Exceptions to our Privacy Policy**

Possible exceptions to our policy include the following circumstances, and as indicated herein, where we would be compelled to release your personal identifying information to a third party or entity:

• If a governmental agency, or an attorney, subpoenas your private information, or makes a formal request for discovery pursuant to any legal action, or pending legal action. 

• If our attorney requests such information relevant to a current or pending legal matter in which you are a potential or actual party or otherwise contributed in some way to the causation of the legal matter. 

**Cookies**

Please note that we employ the use of cookies. Currently we employ cookies when users create user accounts, but we may further employ cookies to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future.

Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions. 

The information gathered is not shared with third parties. You may turn off your cookies by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser. 

Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to turn your cookies off. Cookies do not reveal personal information and if you turn off your cookies you may find your enjoyment of the Internet, and our site, to be reduced or impaired. 

In order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use your email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes. 

Cookies may provide Recording Session information, show us visitor preferences regarding return visits to our website, help us to mange subscription or private areas on our website, record user specific tracking or aggregate tracking information of visitors and deliver user customized content based on user specific information, such as browser type, screen type and resolution and so forth. None of the information gathered is shared with third parties. 

Other possible uses for the information that we collect includes internal tracking, review, or is used for contacting purposes and then is archived by us for future usage. We also use the information we collect to provide custom content for our user base. 

**General Information**

****As we have indicated above, it is our policy not to send unsolicited emails or allow third parties to contact you via the email address that you provide to us. We may, from time to time, contact you to discuss business relevant to your membership and, naturally, we will contact you to respond to inquiries that you may send to us. 

You can access our Website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. Membership signups require the disclosure of certain personal information, which we do not share except as disclosed herein. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from third party sources, such as public records or entities, or private organizations. 

We do not knowingly collect personal data or information from minors. 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measure to protect the personal data that we have under our control. These policies, rules and technical measures help to protect your data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. However, note that no policy, rule or technical measure can offer 100% protection against unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitor’s and members’ personal data.

**Further Data Collection**

We may collect aggregate (general tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site. We also may collect user specific information about pages that users visit on our site. Any information that you give us when you complete a contact form or inquiry form, survey and so forth is collected by us. 

Should you engage in a business transaction with us, such as purchasing a tool, product or service, we will collect the information necessary to complete that transaction.

You may be required to complete online registration forms that provide us with contact information (such as your name and street address), your email address, and your phone numbers. 

We may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our service so that we can directly communicate with you regarding issues we determine to be relevant. 

Please contact us if you should have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy. 

#### Purchasing Services or Products

Any purchase of a service or product from us requires that you provide us your credit card information. We will maintain such information in as secure a manner as meets industry standards and we shall not share any such information with any third party or entity other than as reasonably necessary to fulfill your credit card based order.
